Okay, so do y'all remember this? I know y'all remember this. So during the crazy bananas
buffalo snowstorm, a woman and her boyfriend heard noises from outside of somebody that was in need
and they went outside and it was an elderly mentally disabled man that was in the snow and
was like severely frostbitten. They took him inside their home with their three kids in the
middle of Christmas and saved his life. That woman's name is Shakira Autry and she'll be
joining us on my podcast Small Doses. So if you have any questions for Shakira, please drop them
in the comments because we will be asking some of them on the show and it might be your question
that we choose. Really looking forward to having this unexpected angel on the show and looking
forward to you all hearing it. Drop your questions in the comments and remember Small Doses starting
on February 8th will be on YouTube as well as wherever you get your podcasts.
I told you.